{
    "subject": "resource/Kinetic_Suspension_Technology",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Kinetic Suspension Technology is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems.  The company is based in Dunsborough, Western Australia.Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd, Dunsborough Western Australia in 1999.",
    "human_readable": "Kinetic Suspension Technology is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems. The company is based in Dunsborough, Western Australia. Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd, Dunsborough Western Australia in 1999.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.955451250076294,
            "question": "What is the name of the acquired company that developed passive vehicle suspension systems?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.918867290019989,
            "question": "What type of systems does Kinetic Suspension Technology develop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9034885764122009,
            "question": "Where is Kinetic Suspension Technology headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.879489541053772,
            "question": "What type of technology does Kinetic Suspension Technology specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.868604302406311,
            "question": "What year did Tenneco Automotive acquire Kinetic Ltd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8628868460655212,
            "question": "What industry is Kinetic Suspension Technology involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7812991142272949,
            "question": "In what location was Kinetic Ltd based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7757598757743835,
            "question": "Who acquired Kinetic Ltd in 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7182540893554688,
            "question": "Is Kinetic Suspension Technology still an independent company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.624942421913147,
            "question": "What does Tenneco Automotive do?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kinetic Suspension Technology is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems. The company is based in Dunsborough, Western Australia. Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd, Dunsborough Western Australia in 1999.",
            "html": "dbpedia_909_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kinetic Suspension Technology still an independent company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_909_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who acquired Kinetic Ltd in 1999?",
            "html": "dbpedia_909_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what location was Kinetic Ltd based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_909_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_909_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why:\n\n* **The documents clearly state:** \"Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd of Australia in 1999, an advanced suspension engineering company based in Dunsborough, Western Australia.\"  This directly supports the triple. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information and without prior knowledge, I can evaluate the triple as follows:\n\nThe triple states that \"Kinetic Suspension Technology is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems. The company is based in Dunsborough, Western Australia. Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd, Dunsborough Western Australia in 1999.\"\n\nHere's the evaluation:\n\n* The first statement \"Kinetic Suspension Technology is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems.\" is supported by the documents, as it mentions that \"Patented Kinetic components operate without the need for input from sensors, electronics or the driver\" and also states that \"Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd of Australia in 1999\".\n* The second statement \"The company is based in Dunsborough, Western Australia.\" is supported by the documents, as it mentions that \"Note to editors: Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd of Australia in 1999, an advanced suspension engineering company based in Dunsborough, Western Australia\".\n* The third statement \"Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd, Dunsborough Western Australia in 1999.\" is also supported by the documents, as it mentions that \"Note to editors: Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd of Australia in 1999\".\n\nTherefore, the output is:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information confirms that Kinetic Suspension Technology is involved in developing passive vehicle suspension systems. It also mentions that Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd, which is based in Dunsborough, Western Australia, in 1999. Therefore, the statement aligns with the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}